明星们恨我们 因此拒绝给我们配音
（其实他们这么做还是蛮明智的……
故片中明星均非本人配音 包括耶稣
队长 我要死了吗?
Am I gonna die, captain?
你会没事的 列兵 听见了嘛?
It'll be all right, private. Do you hear me?
你要直视死神的双眼 对他大喊
You need to look that angel of death right in the eye and shout--
卧槽什么鸟玩意?
"what the shit is that?"
- 肌肉男T恤 - 肌肉男T恤?
- Macho man t-shirt. - A macho man t-shirt?
好吧 大家都停下
All right, everyone stop!
天杀的 我都说过了每个人要做到尽量真实 可看看你们
God damn it, I told all of you we need to make this authentic, and look at you.
是啊 你们这些家伙 不知道叛军该长什么样吗?
Uh, yeah, you guys. Don't you know what rebels look like?
唯一严肃对待这次场景重现的只有Kuzniak医生
The only one taking this reenactment seriously is Dr. Kuzniak.
重现? 什么场景重现?
Reenactment? What reenactment?
问个问题 能把他买回家不?
Quick question, can I buy him?
什么狗屁玩意
This some bullshit.
老子懒得鸟你们这帮收棉花的鸟人
I don't give a shit about your cotton-picking problems.
收棉花通常是南方奴隶的差事
我这句用词妙吧?
See what I did there?
你丫给我等着 混蛋
I'ma get you for this, asshole.
抱怨个毛啊 这儿又不止你一个奴隶
Quit complaining. You're not the only slave here.
Denzel 内战重演的重中之重 就是确保历史的准确性
Denzel, the most important thing in civil war reenactment is historical accuracy.
等等 有个...
Hold on. It's a, uh...
来自未来的召唤
A call from the future.
干嘛?
What?
听着 有个老女人打电话来 自称是你老娘
Listen, some old woman called claiming to be your mother.
我跟丫说这玩笑可真没人性 他老娘早死了
I said, "that's a cruel joke. His mom is dead."
然后她就气炸了 说正往这边赶呢
Then she got really upset. She said she's on her way over.
妈咪?
Mommy?
不
No!
队长打头阵啦
Captain's leading the charge.
俺们去干翻那些狗娘养的
Let's get them sumbitches!
太扯了吧 我打中你了
Hey, no fair. I shot you.
跪舔老子的"子蛋"吧 北方佬
Lick my musket balls, yankee.
八十七年前...
Four score and seven--
林肯在念葛底斯堡演说的讲稿
俺们打赢了内战嘿
We just won the civil war.
俺说过南方还会东山再起的吧
I told you the south would rise again.
一切都会跟过去一样兴隆的
It's going to be just like the good old days.
糗了
Awkward.
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ Phuckq ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ 白云苍狗 ♢旗木
联合译制 ❤
幸...
Wheel...
运...
Of...
轮
Fortune!
我是派特·萨加克 本周幸运轮请到的都是双胞胎
I'm Pat Sajak, and it's identical twins week here on wheel.
不然就是我又喝高了
Either that or I'm extremely drunk again.
派特好好笑噢
Pat's so funny.
Connie 你跑哪去了?
Connie, where were you?
整场场景重现你都不在
You missed the whole reenactment.
抱歉 Ethel 我很忙
Oh, sorry, Ethel. I've been busy.
今天是我实现毕生夙愿的日子
Today's the day my lifelong dream will finally come true.
Connie 饭店好几年前就开始往面包皮里加芝士了
Connie, they've been putting cheese in the crust for years now.
不是那个 另一个毕生夙愿
No, my other lifelong dream.
《幸运轮》要来褐丘了
Wheel of Fortune is coming to Hazelhurst.
你看《派仔日报》上写得清清楚楚的
Here, you can read all about it in the Daily Patter.
你订了派特·萨加克的日报?
You subscribe to a daily Pat Sajak newsletter?
订什么啦 我是主编
No, silly, I write it.
为了给选拔赛热身 我已经连看86小时的《幸运轮》了
And I've been watching 86 straight hours of Wheel to get ready for my tryout.
想借点录像回去吗? 每一集我都有
Want to borrow some tapes? I have every episode ever.
这集是录像集锦
This one's a mix tape.
都是爱情字谜噢
All love puzzles.
是时候去露营啦
Time for me to go camp out in line.
噢 派特 人家已经等不及要见到你真人了
Oh, pat, I can't wait to meet you in person.
喔 你真是臭死了
Whoa, you stink.
红色警报啊 Malloy
Code red, Malloy.
我们要在妈咪到来之前好好收拾一下这里
We got to clean this place up before mommy gets here.
走着 我来帮你
Here. Let me help you.
我得清除一下谷歌和必应的搜索记录
I got to clear my google history and my bing history
踩蛋侏儒仔
还有所有问过的关于潮吹的问题
And all the things I asked jeeves ab out squirters.
算了 玩蛋去吧
You know what? Screw it.
要是你妈还活着 那那个罐子装的是谁的骨灰?
If your mom's still alive, then whose ashes are in that urn?
对我语出不敬的前女友
Ex-girlfriend who gave me some lip.
另外这也是个脏话罐
It also doubles as a swear jar.
说脏话就要放一元钱到罐子里
那你之前干嘛要告诉大伙你妈死了?
Why did you tell everybody your mom was dead in the first place?
因为她是个操蛋的噩梦
Because she's a [bleep] nightmare.
记得那是1968年
The year was 1968,
我当时只是个普普通通的美国小男孩
And I was just an average american boy.
自然杂志
儿子
Son!
我的丁丁着火了 我得摩擦灭火啊
Uh, a fire started on my pee pee, and I had to rub it out.
我想是时候让你接受一点启蒙教育了
I think it's time you learned about the birds and the bees.
字面意思是"鸟和蜜蜂"
- 她给你做了性教育 又怎样? - 性教育?
- She talked to you about sex. So what? - About sex?
她把我关在全是鸟和蜜蜂的衣柜里了
She locked me in a closet full of birds and bees!
这就是小男孩偷摸那个脏东西的下场哦
This is what happens to boys who touch their dirty pecker.
就因为你的幼稚 你就剥夺我享受奶奶疼爱的权利?
Just because you're a big baby, you deprived me of a grandmother?
这个人的全职可就是溺爱我啊
The one person whose job it is to spoil me.
有人要为此付出代价
Someone is going to pay for this.
犹太佬吗?
The jews?
我滴个神呐 她来了
Dear god, she's here!
快 得穿上她给我织的圣诞毛衣
Quick! I got to put on this christmas sweater she knitted me.
不要乱摸你的脏蛋
这件还真是"剩蛋"气息浓重
Well, that puts the "christ" in christmas.
Woodrow 我的小宝贝
Woodrow, my dear.
嗨 妈咪
Hi, mommy.
噢 你住的地方真漂亮
Oh, what a lovely home you have here.
呃噢 有灰噢
Uh-oh, dusty.
你小时候也会忘记给盆栽除尘
You forgot to dust our plant when you were little.
所以你把才抛弃了我们
That's why your father left.
我错了 妈咪 我不乖
I'm sorry, mommy. I'm a bad boy.
打我吧 打我吧
Spank me. Spank me!
噢 别犯傻了 Woodrow
Oh, don't be silly, Woodrow.
- 这是初犯 三振才出局呢 - 噢 好吧
- We'll just call that strike one. - Oh, okay.
Malloy 装作啥也没看见
Malloy, forget you saw that.
我倒是想呢
Oh, I wish I could.
你肯定就是我可爱的熊外孙孙了
And you must be my cute little grandcubby.
是的呢 好奶奶
I am, gam-gam.
真是等不及要宠坏我乖孙孙了
Oh, I can't wait to spoil you to death.
可可纯度99%
看见没 Woody 奶奶才不是你说的那种烂婊子呢
See, Woody? Grandma's not a horrible [bleep] like you said.
我开个玩笑嘛
My little comedian.
别听他的 妈咪 我很高兴你能来
Don't listen to him, mommy. I love having you here.
那敢情好 正好养老院也把我赶出来了
Oh, good, because I was thrown out of the nursing home.
看来就算你室友玩宾果游戏作了弊
Apparently when your roommate cheats at bingo,
你也不能剪断她的喂食管
You're not allowed to cut her feeding tube.
所以我打算在这儿常住了
So I'm moving here forever.
- 什么? - 万岁
- What? - Yay!
你可以和Woody住一起
You can have Woody's room.
棒极了
Wonderful.
您这礼拜最好赶着给Woody织一件写"别碰你脏蛋"的毛衣
You ought to make Woody one of those "don't touch your pecker" sweaters...
他病得不轻呢
for every day of the week. He's got a problem.
汽车旅馆 幸运轮今日海选
我爱幸运轮
请问能把字谜解出来吗?
Would you like to solve the puzzle?
那个啥... 喵... 在那... 头戴的... 玩意里
Tuh-hee caht... Eyen...Tuh-hee hawt.
下一位
Next.
好的 转一下幸运轮吧
Okay. Give the wheel a spin.
- 我擦嘞 - 下一位
- Oh, [bleep] this. - Next.
请简单做下自我介绍
Tell us a little something about you.
我叫Connie 如果能见到派特·萨加克 我会兴奋得拉一裤子屎
My name's Connie, and if I ever met Pat Sajak, I'd probably crap myself.
好样的 Connie
Good job, Connie.
- 好的 Connie 第一关是个短语 - 我知道答案是什么
- Okay, Connie. This first one is a phrase-- - I'd like to solve the puzzle.
"梨树旁的鹧鸪"
"a partridge in a pear tree."
我的天
Oh, my god.
简直不可思议 看来最后一位参赛者出现了
That's amazing. Looks like we filled our last slot.
真厉害
Very impressive.
派-派-派特·萨加克?
P-p-pat Sajak?
这张是他第一天上幼儿园的照片
And this is his first day of kindergarten.
我想大家都知道他坐的是什么车
I think we all know what bus he was riding.
那天我去了六趟学校
I had to come to school six times that day.
因为他想妈咪了吗?
Because he missed his mommy?
哪儿呀 因为他17岁以前啥都不吃就吃我的奶头
No, because he refused to consume anything but my breast milk until he was 17.
都是你逼我吃的
You made me do that!
你说固体食物会让我得小儿麻痹症
You said solid food would give me polio.
再说一遍 Woodrow?
What's that, Woodrow?
呃 妈妈的奶奶好香甜呀
Uh, mommy milk is nummy yummy.
天 哪里来了这么一位皮肤皱巴骨头软塌的美女?
Damn, who's the kinky hottie with the wrinkly body?
噢不 噢不不 不 别打她主意 不要
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. No, you don't. No way.
请叫我Denzel
Call me Denzel.
天呐
Oh, my.
哎呀 你一定是这世上最可爱的年轻人吧?
Well, aren't you just the sweetest young man?
我叫Anita Johnson
Anita Johnson.
很好 因为一会儿你肯定会被我惊艳到的
Good, 'cause you about to get a big one.
你确实是个令人惊艳的小伙子
You certainly come on strong.
我还有很多地方能惊艳到你呢 带你见识见识呗?
Oh, I come on a lot of things. Want me to show you?
够了 Denzel 快滚出去
All right, Denzel. Get out of here!
噢 我的宝贝来脾气了
Oh, my baby's upset.
没准他需要来点妈妈那甜甜的奶奶
Maybe he needs some of mommy's nummy yummy.
说得对 Malloy
Great idea, Malloy.
不用不用不用 我早餐吃不少了
Oh, no, no, no! I had a big breakfast.
快吸 Woodrow
Suck it, Woodrow.
这奶过期了
Milk's gone bad.
那我... 什么时候再来录节目?
So, uh, what time should I be here for the taping?
Connie 保险理算员告诉我们
Connie, the insurance adjuster is telling us
我们放把火把这楼给烧了是最明智的
The smartest thing to do would be to set fire to this building.
就连这大楼底下的土地
Even the soil on which this building stands
都会因此贫瘠化 数代人无法于此耕种
Has been rendered barren for generations to come.
简而言之就是 不会录节目了
So short answer, there will be no taping.
不给你录 永远不录 消失吧
Not for you, not ever, please go.
不 我不能走
No! I can't go!
这是我的梦想
This is my dream!
这儿来了个瞎转的 麻了她 把她带走
We got a spinner. Tranq her and yank her.
破产
妈咪 听我说 你得离Denzel这家伙远点
Mommy, listen. You got to stay away from this Denzel guy.
他很危险
He's trouble.
相信我 他每天早上都会吃老妪
Trust me, he eats old ladies for breakfast.
噢 你不用和我说啦 儿子
Oh, you don't need to tell me, son.
他现在就在吃我呢
He's doing that to me right now.
咋的 Woody?
'Sup, Woody?
你这狗畜生 我干死你
You son of a bitch! I'll kill you!
Woody 住手 哪儿有这么对爸爸的?
Woody, stop. That's no way to treat your father.
我爸爸?
My father?
你没听明白? 我们结婚了
Oh, you didn't hear? We got married.
我现在是你老爹
I'm your daddy.
早上好呀 儿子
Good morning, son.
但愿昨晚你妈的尖叫没害你睡不着
I hope all that screaming your mama did last night didn't keep you up.
- 我没听到 - 是嘛?
- I didn't notice. - Really?
那你总该听到我的蛋蛋...
Well, how about the sound of my balls
撞她那又肥又老的屁股了吧?
Slapping against her big old ass?
这你肯定听得见
You had to hear that.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're doing.
你只不过是拿这套来报复我让你演奴隶这事
You're just getting back at me for the whole slave thing,
但你做得太过分了 Denzel
But you have gone too far, Denzel.
拜托 叫我老爹
Please, call me daddy.
我叫你个狗东... 懂得儿子的最佳老爹
I'll call you a son of a-- bestest daddy in the whole wide world.
早上好呀 男孩们
Good morning, boys.
早啊 宝贝
Morning, baby.
没想到你这老腰还挺得起来
I'm surprised you can walk straight.
嘿 小伙子 快去厨房给老爹拿罐啤酒来
Hey, boy, run into the kitchen and grab your daddy a beer.
你没权利对我指手划脚
You are not the boss of me!
Woodrow Denzel现在是你爸爸
Woodrow, Denzel is your father now,
他说什么 你就得做什么 明白?
And you're going to do what he says. Understand?
但是... 明白 妈咪
But... Yes, mommy.
就让我和你享受天伦之乐吧 我的儿
Me and you, we're gonna have a lot of fun, son.
你好 派特
Hi, Pat.
傻瓜绑架指南
我这是在哪?
Where am I?
救命 来人救救我
Help. Someone help me!
放轻松 派特
Relax, Pat.
我们会成为好朋友的
We're going to be best friends.
你? 你是那个喷屎的娘们儿
You? You're the shit woman.
你要做什么?
What do you want?
摸上去就和看上去一样完美
It feels as perfect as it looks.
快滚开 疯色鬼
Get away from me, you crazy stalker.
我可不是什么疯色鬼
I'm not a crazy stalker.
你问问背面小派吧
Just ask Back-Pat.
你好 派特 我是背面小派
Well, hello there, Pat. I'm Back-Pat.
听着 我不知道你想从我这儿得到什么
Look, I'm not sure what you want from me,
- 但是... - 快回礼 派特
- but-- - Say hello back, Pat.
我不明白 你是让"背面小派"再打招呼呢
I'm confused. Are you telling Back-Pat to say hello again,
还是让我向"背面小派"打招呼?
Or do you want me to say hello back to Back-Pat?
别特么耍嘴皮啊 姓萨的
Don't [bleep] with me, Sajak.
虽然我爱你 爱你这除过皱的小嫩皮儿
Just because I love you and your smooth botoxed skin
耍花招我一样会拆了你的后脊梁
Doesn't mean I won't snap your goddamn spine!
小心喔 我觉得她有病
Be careful. I think she's crazy.
嘿 你搞毛啊? 我在看冰球赛呢
Hey! What are you doing? I'm watching the hockey game.
给我闭肛
Shut your ass up!
哎呦 白种人哪
Man, white people.
你们懂的
You know what I'm saying?
这特么有毛好笑啊?
What's so goddamn funny?
儿子别吵
Quiet, boy.
白唉唉唉唉种人哪
Whi-I-I-I-I-ite people!
真没想到还有这么一手
I did not see that coming.
老子受不了啦
I can't take this crap!
- 受够你这些狗屁了 - 住手
- I'm sick of your bullshit! - Stop it!
不管喜不喜欢 咱现在是一家人了
Like it or not, we are a family now.
今天你俩必须好好相处一下
You two need to spend the day together
拿出个父子的样儿
Like father and son.
- 可是妈咪... - Anita 我可不想这样
- But, mommy-- - Oh, Anita, I don't want to.
这事没商量
No arguments!
遵命 陛下
Yes, ma'am.
怎么不高兴啊 Malloy?
Oh, what's the matter, Malloy?
粑粑和Denzel爷爷掐架呢
Daddy and grandpa Denzel were fighting.
好怕怕哟 好奶奶
I'm scared, gam-gam.
你这只可怜小熊仔儿
Oh, you poor little bear.
拿去花 这叠百元大钞是从Woody内裤抽屉里找到的
Here, I found this stack of hundreds in woody's underwear drawer.
白种人啊 你们懂的
White people. You know what I'm saying.
一个给我 一个给派特
One for me and one for Pat
四个给我 一个给派特
And four for me and one for Pat.
Connie 你干嘛呢?
Connie, what are you doing?
你拿了十人份的食物哎
You're taking enough food for ten people.
通常你只拿九人份的
You usually only take enough for nine.
有一个很好的理... 呃... 很好的解...
Um, there's a good re-- uh, a good explana--
电视巨星派特·萨加克神秘失踪已进入第二天
Day two in the mysterious disappearance of television icon Pat Sajak.
失踪
最后露面是在旅馆
Last seen at his hotel,
证人声称 当时附近有某种巨型橙色海牛出没
witnesses report seeing some sort of giant orange sea cow in the vicinity.
警方素描
Connie在囤食物 派特·萨加克与此同时失踪了?
Connie's hoarding food, and Pat Sajak is missing?
Steve 你盘算清楚没有?
Steve, are you doing the math on this?
清了
Yes.
奶子一对
Boobies!
计算器上摁出5318008 倒着看像英文BOOBIES
这儿风景挺好哒
It is kind of nice out here.
我来这儿全是我妈逼的
I'm only here because mommy's making me.
我的烂人榜上永远有你大名
You are on my everlasting shit list!
好啦 之前我的确有点打击报复 但...
Okay, look, I was a little hard on you, but...
现在我觉得咱俩扯平了
I'd say we're even now.
而且我也挺喜欢你娘的
Plus I really do like your mama.
随你怎么说
Whatever.
靠啊 我不知道这钩子怎么装饵
Oh, damn it. I don't know how to bait this hook.
这样就行了
Here you go.
你爹从来没带你钓过鱼?
Didn't your dad ever take you fishing?
只有一次 那个妓女花了一整晚
Only once, and it took that hooker all night
才把她双拳深深插进我...
To get her fists deep up my--
哦 你问"钓鱼"啊
Oh, "fishing."
没 没带过
No, he didn't.
钓到了 钓到了
Oh, I got one. I got one!
别放跑了 快收线
Oh, get him! Reel him in!
快上来了
I got him.
我们成功了
We got him.
干得好 儿子 这鱼真不错
Good job, son. This a nice fish.
它咬我
He bit me.
靠 操翻这死鱼
Man, [bleep] that fish.
哎哟 我的腿
Ouch! My leg!
你们特么...
You goddamn--
天哪
Oh, my god.
我就知道
I knew it.
她杀了派特·萨加克还分尸了
She killed Pat Sajak and chopped him up.
我看不见呢
I'm not seeing that.
我勒个去 Ethel死了
Oh, my god. Ethel's dead!
那你特么是谁?
Then who the hell are you?
我才是Ethel
I'm Ethel.
你是Ethel的话 我肯定是...
Then if you're Ethel, I must be...
派特·萨加克
Pat Sajak!
我脸上肯定戴了面罩
So this is a mask!
粘得还真牢哇
It's stuck on there pretty good.
好 也许动刀就可以了
Okay, maybe this knife will help.
爽
Oh, yeah.
好哎 割下来了 割下来了
Okay, it's working! It's working!
我不是派特·萨加克 我是骷髅哥
I'm not Pat Sajak! I'm a skeleton!
白种人这梗现在我懂了
White people, now I get it!
本周末 父子野餐会
你还好么 Woody?
Hey, uh, everything cool, Woody?
还好 就是...
Yeah. It's just...
其实 有人周末要办父子野餐会
Well, they're having a father-son picnic this weekend,
我感觉好难过
and it makes me sad.
难过他们都把广告打到酒吧来了?
That they have to advertise these things in bars?
不是 是因为有一次我爹答应带我去野餐
No, because my dad promised to take me to one once,
但根本没露面
But he never showed.
都怪我没给那狗日的植物掸灰
If only I'd dusted that [bleep] plant.
嘿 不如这样
Hey, you know what?
我带你去参加父子野餐会好了
I'll take you to the father-son picnic.
你真的肯带我去?
You'd really do that for me?
我还是想买你的黑奴
I still want to buy your slave.
- 就是他 - 他不是黑奴
- Him. - He's not a slave!
他是我爸
He's my father.
不好 九点半了
Uh-oh. It's 9:30.
妈咪让我九点前回家的
Mommy told me to be home at 9:00.
别担心你妈 现在可是老爹的亲子时间
Don't worry about your mama. This is father-and-son time.
咱们齐心协力开了这王八蛋的脑袋
Now let's bash this mother[bleep]'s skull in together
亲子时间
Father-son time!
嘘 我妈是羊羊
Shh. My mom's a sheep.
我说"是羊羊"了? 其实我想说"睡觉觉"
Did I say "sheep"? I meant to say "asleep."
Woodrow 你没按时回来喔
Woodrow, you missed your curfew.
我该怎么惩罚你呢?
What am I going to do with you?
我有个主意
I got an idea.
派特 你等着看我准备的惊喜吧
Oh, Pat, have I got a surprise for you.
请别告诉我你还有"正面小派"
Please don't tell me there's a front Pat.
你觉得如何?
What do you think?
现在你可以跟我永远活在游戏里了
Now you can live the game with me forever.
幸...
Wheel...
运...
Of...
轮
Fortune!
哎哟天哪
Oh, my god!
Connie绑架了一个隆帕小矮人
Connie kidnapped an oompa loompa!
《查理的巧克力工厂》中喜爱巧克力的小矮人
那是派特·萨加克 你个傻缺
That's Pat Sajak, you idiot.
也对 小矮人没那么矮 颜色也没那么橙
Right. Oompa loompas aren't that short and orange.
我报警吧
I'm calling the cops.
报警的话 派特就没命了
If you do that, Pat Sajak will die.
你们的朋友Connie已经疯了
Your friend Connie has snapped.
如果你们想要救他的命 就得照我说的做
If you want to save his life, you will do as I say.
- 你哪位? - 请叫我"谣言扩散器"
- Who are you? - Name's Buzz Buzzer.
我是真人秀《人质》的洽谈人
I'm a professional game show "host-age" negotiator.
话说当红竞赛节目主持人经常被绑架吗?
How often are popular game show hosts held hostage?
超乎你想象 2012年《家庭骗局》
More than you think. 2012, Family Feud.
1976年开播的家庭对抗节目
你以为主持人理查德·道森是自然死亡吗?
You think Richard Dawson died of natural causes?
2006年《强棒出击》
2006, Press Your Luck.
1983年开播的综艺节目
你以为彼得·汤玛肯是退休了?
You think Peter Tomarken retired?
《美国舞台》节目主持人 去世原因实为心脏病
迪克·克拉克遭绑架杀害后 被抛尸在了七个地方
Dick Clark was kidnapped and killed on seven separate occasions.
我们只能去找一些像他的人去主持
We had to keep tracking down look-alikes.
所谓中风去世的那位
By the time he had the stroke,
其实是第十任迪克了
We were on our tenth Dick.
听来Ethel这周末约炮前戏缓慢呀
Sounds like Ethel on a slow weekend.
顺便说下 好奶奶给我买的骚车
Gam-gam bought me this, by the way.
回见了 傻X们
See you later, assholes.
该死 Woody
Damn, Woody.
你要是再不挺起腰板儿
That woman's never going to stop treating you like a child
那娘们会一辈子拿你当孩子
unless you stand up for yourself.
霸气点 老子可不是养怂逼的
Be a man. I raised you better than that.
知道吗 老爹? 你说得对
You know what, dad? You're right.
是时候挺起我的腰板儿了
It is time for me to stand up for myself.
那帮傻X鸟把我的筋给挑了
Those [bleep] birds ate my hamstrings.
一旦进去 你们就是选手了 游戏正式开始
Once you're in, just act like contestants and play the game.
等Connie赢了 趁她高兴分神
When Connie wins, the euphoria will distract her.
你抓住萨加克 赶紧往外跑
Then you grab sajak and get out.
如果这畜生输了
If the crimson beast loses,
游戏结束
Game over.
Anita 你儿子有话对你说
Anita, your son has something to say to you.
想说啥?
What is it?
您是全宇宙最美丽的妈咪 拜
Uh, you are the prettiest mommy in the whole world. Bye.
Woody 跟她说
Woody, tell her.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
妈咪 你让杀人蜂和嗜血乌鸦咬我
Uh, mommy, when you let africanized bees and bloodthirsty crows attack me,
这是不对的 我...
It's not nice, and I--
我不想你再这么做了
I don't want you to do that anymore.
我不知道诶
Oh, I had no idea.
要是用这生锈的车链子抽你 你高兴了不?
Would it make you feel any better if I whipped you with a rusty bicycle chain?
诶呀 上帝啊
Oh, Jesus Christ!
你 是你怂恿他这么做的
And you! You put him up to this.
你把我儿子带坏了
You're a bad influence on my son.
少特么这么和我说话 老娘们
Don't you talk that way to me, woman.
贱人 你以为全世界就你趁车链子吗?
Bitch, you think you're the only one with a bicycle chain?
我猜有个e
I'd like to buy an e.
我爱派特的南瓜头
你不会真以为我会和你玩这个疯狂游戏吧?
You don't really expect me to play along with this insanity, do you?
干嘛不
Yeah.
难不成你想要我切下你的脸 喂给背面小派吃
Unless you want me to cut off your face and feed it to back-pat.
有没有e呢?
Do we have any es?
Steve? Ethel?
你们来《幸运轮》现场干啥?
What are you doing on Wheel of Fortune?
我们来参加比赛呀 Connie
We're here to play the game, Connie.
不好意思 Gary Charlene
Sorry, Gary. Sorry, Charlene.
你们时间到了 感谢参与
Your time is up. Thanks for playing.
都特么给我去死吧
Goddamn mother[bleep]!
救命 我这么土豪这么叼 不能死啊 我可是派特·萨加克啊
Help me, please! I'm too rich and important to die. I'm Pat [bleep] Sajak.
五千刀? 该死
$5,000? Crap.
记着 Steve 咱得输啊
Remember, Steve, you gotta lose.
快猜字母q
Guess the letter q.
真会出馊主意
That's a terrible idea.
我打赌这字谜里都是q
I bet this puzzle's full of qs.
有没有s呢?
Is there an s?
有五个s呢
There are five ses.
卧槽 不勒个是吧?
Huh. What are the odds of that?
她会把你们全干掉的
She's going to murder you all.
- 你特么敢碰我 - 住手
- Don't touch me with that! - Stop it!
Woodrow 我们要告诉你一件事
Woodrow, there's something we have to tell you.
儿子 你妈和我要离婚了
Son, your mama and I are getting a divorce.
不 全都赖我
Oh, no! It's my fault.
Woody 这不赖你啦
Oh, Woody, it's not your fault.
离婚仙子来了 施了个分离魔法
The divorce fairy came and spriencle some seperation dust
不赖你赖狗啊
Of course it's your fault!
不 我又害爸妈离婚了
Oh, no! I did it again!
也许我就不配有个爹
Maybe I wasn't meant to have a daddy.
别听她的 才不是你的错呢
Aw, don't listen to her. This ain't your fault.
你是个好孩子 Woody 疯了的是你妈
You're a good boy, Woody. You just got a crazy-ass mama.
那... 咱们还是会去亲子野游的 对吗?
Well, we can still go to the father-son picnic, right?
咱们都不是父子了
Not if we're not father and son.
他们定的规矩
Them's the rules.
只剩一个办法能结束这痛苦了
There's only one thing that's going to end this pain.
Steve 你在干嘛?
Steve, what are you doing?
咱们应该要输的 你个傻缺
You're supposed to lose, you dipshit.
你以为我不想啊
I'm trying to lose.
你能来猜出这个字谜吗 Steve?
Would you like to solve the puzzle, Steve?
Steve 答都不要答
Steve, don't even answer.
你给我滚蛋 Ethel
Get off my ballsack, Ethel.
答对了
That's correct.
这个字谜就是弗雷德·默茨在《我爱露茜》中说过的一句台词
The category was "things that Fred Mertz should have said on I love lucy."
1957年开播的美国情景喜剧 剧中女主角也叫Ethel
Steve赢了
And Steve is the winner.
Connie可不会输
Connie's not supposed to lose!
Connie出击
Connie smash!
恶搞绿巨人
救命啊 我要被这个320斤的怪物挤碎了
Help! I'm being crushed by a 350-pound monster.
回答正确 答案就是...
That's correct. The category was
瑞贝尔·威尔森的沙发会说的话
"things Rebel Wilson's couch might say."
澳大利亚女演员 体态丰腴
真不敢相信我会中了那个黑鬼用鸡鸡施下的巫毒咒
Oh, I can't believe I let myself fall under the voodoo spell of that black man's dick.
你知道我从你内衣橱里拿出来的那些钱吧?
You know all the money I took out of your underwear drawer?
我觉得是他从我钱包里偷走了 肯定的
I think he stole some of that out of my purse--typical.
不许你这么说他
Don't you ever talk that way about him.
你找抽是不?
Does somebody need a spanking?
抽你妹
Screw your spankings.
Danzel是对的 我受够被你呼来唤去了
Denzel's right. I am done being pushed around by you.
爸爸走了才不是因为我
I'm not the reason daddy left.
是因为你
You are!
你说什么 Woody?
What are you saying, Woody?
对不起啊 妈咪 这么说有点过分
Sorry, mommy. That was a little harsh.
我真正想说的是...
I guess what I really meant to say is:
快特么给我滚吧
Get the [bleep] out!
不要 好奶奶 不许走
No, gam-gam, don't go.
我... 我还要礼物
I n-- I need more presents.
我是说 我爱你
I m-- I mean I love you.
我已经没钱了 Malloy
I don't have any more money, Malloy.
赶紧去死吧
Choke on my balls.
你个混蛋
You bastard.
你让我爱上你 爱上你那猜字谜的渊博知识
You made me love you and your godlike knowledge of the alphabet,
最后你却让我输
and then you made me lose.
现在你要你死 派特
Now you must die, Pat!
我不要再失去主持人了
I am not losing another one.
我拖住她 救萨加克
I'll hold her off! Save Sajak!
把我的派特还给我
Give me back my Pat!
等下 我们这么拼命救派特·萨加克图个毛?
Wait, why are we risking our lives for Pat Sajak?
求求你不要伤害我 让我做啥都行
Please don't hurt me. I'll do anything.
啥都行?
Anything?
下面掌声有请我的可爱搭档
And please welcome my lovely cohost.
嗨 派特
Hi, Pat.
亲子野游
爸爸 这个人是谁?
Daddy, who's that man?
像个恋童癖呢 儿子
Looks like a pedophile, son.
他才不是恋童癖 他是我儿子
Hey, he's no pedophile. He's my son.
Danzel 你来啦
Denzel, you came!
好了 咱来整死这帮五岁大的小屁孩
Shh, now let's crush these five-year-old skulls...
一起整
Together.
♪ 父子齐心 ♪
♪ Teamwork ♪
♪ 你知道齐心协力我们所向披靡 ♪
♪ You know we're going to do it together ♪
跨种族恋童癖二人组破坏野游
♪ 父子齐心 ♪
♪ Teamwork ♪
♪ 你和我打遍天下无敌手 ♪
♪ You and me will make it forever ♪
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons